<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Josh Marks&#39; Blog!</title>
    <link>http://example.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Josh Marks&#39; Blog!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 20:21:44 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Books I&#39;ve Known and Loved</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 20:21:44 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/books/</guid>
      <description>A non-exhaustive list of books I&amp;rsquo;ve really enjoyed and am glad I bought for my bookshelf at home. Let me know if you find a gem! Or if you have a book that I should check out. I&amp;rsquo;m always looking for a well written book.
Electrical Engineering  High-Speed Digital Design: A Handbook of Black Magic High Speed Signal Propogation: Advanced Black Magic Electromagnetic Compatibility Engineering The Art of Electronics The Art of Electronics: The x Chapters Massive MIMO Networks: Spectral, Energy, and Hardware Efficiency:  Satellite Communications Payload and System Microwave Oven Repair Building Electro-Optical Systems: Making It all Work The Design of CMOS Radio-Frequency Integrated Circuits Switching Power Supplies A - Z Understanding Delta-Sigma Data Converters Analog Circuit Design: A Tutorial Guide to Applications and Solutions  Software Engineering  Test Driven Development for Embedded C Artificial Intelligence: A Modern Approach The Clean Coder: A Code of Conduct for Professional Programmers Structure and Interpretation of Computer Programs Design Patterns: Elements of Reusable Object-Oriented Software HCS08 Unleashed: Designer&amp;rsquo;s Guide To the HCS08 Microcontrollers  Math  Linear Algebra Data-Driven Science and Engineering: Machine Learning, Dynamical Systems, and Control The Art of Problem Solving, Vol.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Current Feedback Op-amp Testing</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/current-feedback-opamp-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 10:09:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/current-feedback-opamp-testing/</guid>
      <description>Big takeaway: Current feedback opamps are very particular about external component values. You must choose from the list of approved values in the datasheet or spend a lot of time hunting for an optimum value that gives you the gain and also provides stability.
Summary: I replaced the feedback resistor elements with 510 ohm resistors for Rf and Rg. This gives a gain of two and the widest bandwidth, 1.4GHz, from the OPA695.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
